bedbug.com 2015-12-29

# Find bed bug products safely at Bedbug.com

Last updated on 20/June/2011

Bedbug.com takes your right to privacy seriously, and wants you to feel comfortable using this web site. This privacy policy deals with personally-identifiable information (referred to as "Personal Data" below) that may be collected by this site. This policy only applies to www.bedbug.com. Bedbug.com is a licensee of the McAfee Security Program. This privacy statement covers the web site www.bedbug.com. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact[customerservice@bedbug.com](mailto:customerservice@bedbug.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).  
   
E. U. SAFE HARBOR POLICY

Bedbug.com recognizes that privacy is very important to our customers, and we pledge to protect the security and privacy of any personal information that customers provide to us. This includes customer's names, addresses, telephone numbers, email addresses and any information that can be linked to an individual. Not only does Bedbug.com strive to collect, use and disclose personal information in a manner consistent with the laws of the countries in which it does business, but it also has a tradition of upholding the highest ethical standards in its business practices. This Safe Harbor Privacy Policy (the "Policy") sets forth the privacy principles that Bedbug.com follows with respect to transfers of personal information from the European Union (EU) to the United States. 

SAFE HARBOR 

The United States Department of Commerce and the European Commission have agreed on a set of data protection principles and frequently asked questions (the "Safe Harbor Principles") to enable U.S. companies to satisfy the EU law requirement that personal information transferred from the EU to the United States be adequately protected. Consistent with its pledge to protect personal privacy, Bedbug.com adheres to the Safe Harbor Principles. 

SCOPE 

This Safe Harbor Privacy Policy (the "Policy") applies to all personal information received by Bedbug.com in the United States from the EU, in any format including electronic, paper or verbal. 

DEFINITIONS  
   
The following definitions shall apply throughout this Policy: "Agent" means any third party that uses personal information provided to Bedbug.com to perform tasks on behalf of and under the instructions of Bedbug.com. "Bedbug.com" means Bedbug.com, its successors, subsidiaries, divisions and groups in the United States. "Personal information" means any information or set of information that identifies or could be used by or on behalf of Bedbug.com to identify an individual. Personal information does not include information that is encoded, anonymized, aggregated or publicly available information that has not been combined with non-public personal information. "Sensitive personal information" means personal information that reveals race, ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or trade union membership, or that concerns health or sex life. In addition, Bedbug.com will treat as sensitive personal information any information received from a third party where that third party treats and identifies the information as sensitive. 

PRIVACY PRINCIPLES  
   
The privacy principles in this Policy are based on the Safe Harbor Principles. 

NOTICE  
   
When Bedbug.com collects personal information directly from individuals in the EU, it will inform them about the purposes for which it collects and uses their personal information, the types of non-agent third parties, if any, to which Bedbug.com discloses that information, and the choices and means, if any, that Bedbug.com offers individuals for limiting the use and disclosure of their personal information. Notice will be provided in clear and conspicuous language when individuals are first asked to provide personal information to Bedbug.com, or as soon as practicable thereafter, and in any event before Bedbug.com uses the information for a purpose other than that for which it was originally collected. If Bedbug.com receives personal information from its subsidiaries, affiliates or other entities in the EU, it will use such information in accordance with the notices such entities provided and the choices made by the individuals to whom such personal information relates. 

CHOICE  
   
Bedbug.com will offer individuals the opportunity to choose (opt-out) whether their personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party, or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. For sensitive personal information, Bedbug.com will give individuals the opportunity to affirmatively and explicitly (opt-in) consent to the disclosure of the information to a non-agent third party or the use of the information for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. Bedbug.com will provide individuals with reasonable methods to exercise their choices. 

DATA INTEGRITY  
   
Bedbug.com will use personal information only in ways that are compatible with the purposes for which it was collected or subsequently authorized by the individual. Bedbug.com will take reasonable steps to ensure that personal information is relevant to its intended use, accurate, complete, and current. 

TRANSFERS TO AGENTS  
   
Bedbug.com will obtain assurances from its agents that they will safeguard personal information consistently with this Policy. If Bedbug.com has knowledge that an agent is using or disclosing personal information in a manner contrary to this Policy, Bedbug.com will take reasonable steps to prevent or stop the use or disclosure. 

ACCESS AND CORRECTION  
   
Upon request, Bedbug.com will grant individuals reasonable access to personal information that it holds about them, and Bedbug.com will take reasonable steps to permit individuals to correct, amend, or delete information that is demonstrated to be inaccurate or incomplete. 

SECURITY  
   
Bedbug.com will take reasonable precautions to protect personal information in its possession from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. 

ENFORCEMENT  
   
Bedbug.com will conduct compliance audits of its relevant privacy practices to verify adherence to this Policy. Any employee that Bedbug.com determines is in violation of this policy will be subject to disciplinary action up to and including termination of employment. 

DISPUTE RESOLUTION  
   
Any questions or concerns regarding the use or disclosure of personal information should be directed to Bedbug.com email address given below. Bedbug.com will investigate and attempt to resolve complaints and disputes regarding use and disclosure of personal information in accordance with the principles contained in this Policy. For complaints that cannot be resolved between Bedbug.com and the complainant, Bedbug.com has agreed to participate in the dispute resolution procedures of the panel established by the European data protection authorities to resolve disputes pursuant to the Safe Harbor Principles. 

CONTACT INFORMATION  
   
Questions or comments regarding this Policy should be submitted to Bedbug.com e-mail as follows: 

or by mail at: 

Bedbug.com/Privacy Policy  
711 S. Carson Street  
Carson City, NV 89701 

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

This Policy may be amended from time to time, consistent with the requirements of the Safe Harbor Principles. Bedbug.com will provide appropriate public notice about such amendments. 

EFFECTIVE DATE: 01/OCT/2009 

Third-Party Service Providers We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal data needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 

CREDIT CARD SECURITY  
   
You can safely enter your entire card number which is considered to be sensitive information on Bedbug.com via our secure server, which encrypts all submitted personal data and sensitive information on that page via secure socket layer (SSL). 

SECURITY 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal data submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Changes to this privacy policy If we decide to change our privacy practices, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we change how we use your personal data, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. No Guarantees While this privacy policy states standards for maintenance of data, and while efforts will be made to meet the said standards, Bedbug.com is not in a position to guarantee compliance with these standards. There may be factors beyond the site editor's control that may result in disclosure of data. Consequently, Bedbug.com offers no warranties or representations as regards maintenance or non-disclosure of data. 

CONTACT INFORMATION

If you have any questions about this policy or about this web site, please feel free to contact us at customerservice@bedbug.com. Editing or deleting your account information If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or amend it by making the change within the my account section of the site, or by contacting emailing our Customer Support at:

or by mail at: 

Bedbug.com/Privacy Policy  
711 S. Carson Street  
Carson City, NV 89701 

MINORS  
   
Bedbug.com does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of 13. Collection of data Registration for an account on this site requires only a valid e-mail address.. You are not required to provide any other information if you do not want to during the registration process. However, during the check out process you are required to give us your name, email address, mailing address and credit card number. We use this information to create your account, for billing purposes and to fill your order. If you use the contact us form you re required to give us your name and email address, we will use this information to respond to your inquiry.  
   
On occasion we will use your email address to send you strictly service related emails. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. As on many web sites, the site editor may also automatically receive general information that is contained in server log files, such as your IP address, and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if it is indeed the site editor's policy to display advertising) is set forth below.  
   
USE OF PERSONAL DATA  
   
Personal Data may be used to customize and improve your user experience on this site. Efforts will be made to prevent your personal data from being made available to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) your consent is obtained, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out for the sharing of data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires interaction with a third party, or is provided by a third party, such as an application service provider; (iv) pursuant to legal action or law enforcement; (v) it is found that your use of this site violates the site editor's policy, terms of service, or other usage guidelines, or if it is deemed reasonably necessary by Bedbug.com to protect Bedbug.com rights and/or property; or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party, in which case that third party will be able to use the personal data in the same manner as set forth in this policy. In the event you choose to use links displayed on this web site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies published on those sites. We will maintain the confidentiality of your personal data, and it will be used only to support your relationship with Bedbug.com, except in such cases as referred to in (vii) above. 

COOKIES  
   
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies to enhance your user experience and to remember your email address and password so that you do not have to enter it each time. Advertisements may display on this web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer; such cookies are subject to the privacy policy of the parties providing the advertisement. However, the parties providing the advertising do not have access to this site's cookies. These parties usually use non-personally-identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to this site. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

ADDTHIS

We use the ‘addthis’ widget on this site to allow our users to tell their friends about the site, by allowing them to send a one time email within the widget, inviting their friend to visit the site. We do not have access to any of the Personal Information collected within this widget. We also use the ‘addthis’ widget to allow users to log into their third party social networking accounts and share a link to bedbug.com with their friends. We have no access to your personal account logins or passwords. Bedbug.com does not share, rent, sell or trade Personal Data with third parties for their promotional purposes. We reserve the right to disclose your personal data as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.
